

JUNIOR FRONTEND DEVELOPER

CHRISTIAN A.SANCHEZ

GET IN CONTACT

Home: 04-504-4086 Mobile: 096-3787611 Mail: christianabrahamsanchez@gmail.com GitHub: Chrisnewgear (github.com) Web: www.chrisnewgeardev.com (under development) Netlify: https://app.netlify.com/teams/chrisnewgear/overview

Current address: Cdla. Colinas de la Alborada Mz. 726 V. 18

PERSONAL PROFILE

I'm a autodidact Junior Frontend Developer with 1 year of experience, with skills in interactive design with 3 years of experience. I am also passionate and willing to learn new technologies to enhance my skills in coding and design, furthermore, I am studying software developing career at "Tecnológico Universitario ARGOS".

AREAS OF EXPERTISE

- HTML, CSS, SQL, JavaScript, JQuery, Git, GitHub, Wordpress, Debian based Linux Distros.
- Basic knowledge of PHP, JAVA, C, C++.
- Photoshop, Illustrator, Premiere Pro, Adobe XD.
- PCs, laptops & Mac repairing.

OTHER SKILLS

- The ability to analyze complex technical information
- · Detail oriented
- · Excellent problem solver
- Fast & comprehensive reading 2000wpm (currently)
- · Drawing & Illustration
- Soft skills
- · English C1 level

WORK EXPERIENCE

ALTURA

SQL Administrator(Currently)

· SQL DBs management

TEDU (AGRICULTORES DEL ECUADOR)

Frontend Developer (2021 - 2022)

- Frontend developer
- · Technical support & consulting

UTEG

Clerk | 2019-2020

- Customer service
- · Technical support

BANCO GUAYAQUIL

Senior Assistant | 2005 - 2016

- · Document digitalization department
- Clearing house
- · Legal requirements
- · Technical support

EDUCATION HISTORY

ESCUELA POLITÉCNICA DEL LITORAL

System Analyst, 2005-2006 (Dropped out)

TECNOLÓGICO UNIVERSITARIO ARGOS

Software Development (Currently)

UDEMY

Web Development with HTML, CSS, JavaScript, JQuery, AJAX, PHP, SQL.

ΡΙ ΔΤ7Ι

- Software Development School (Currently)
- Soft Skills School (Currently)

PÍLDORAS INFORMÁTICAS

• JAVA development (Currently)

LINKEDIN LEARNING

- Graphic design(Currently)
- Full Stack Development (Currenty)